>> 凯尔 - 辛普森:
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: A takeaway, or
一种概括的方法，如何避免双等号的角落个案。
a way to summarize, how to avoid these
corner cases with the double equals.
这些是我认为你可以使用的一套准则。
These are a set of guidelines
that I think you can use.
您可以使用双等号，但在这些特定方案中避免使用。
You can use double equals, but
avoid it in these particular scenarios.
第一，当它们的任一侧可以是 0时，避免双等号，或者
Number one, avoid the double equals
when either side of them can be a 0, or
空字符串，甚至是其中只有空格的字符串。
an empty string, or even one of those
strings with only whitespace in it.
在这些情况下不要使用双等号。
Don't use double equals in those cases.
你可能被咬了很多角的地方
There's just a lot of corner cases
that you might get bitten by.
有些人说很好我不能
Some people say well, I can't, no.
好吧但你还是要重组你的代码好吗
Okay, but is there anyway for
you to restructure your codes so you can?
我觉得这样好多了
Cuz I think that's better.
这至少是个更好的代码不管你喜欢不喜欢
It's at least a better code, regardless
of whether you like double equal or not.
但让我们说你不能
But let's say you can't.
那么另一个你应该问的
Well, then another check
that you should ask or
避免双重等号 >> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 不要用它
to avoid the double equals,
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Don't use it with
非原语。
non-primitives.
我甚至不把它和他们的身份对比
I don't even use it with
the identity comparison on them,
虽然我知道这很有用
even though I know it works.
但是要超级安全，我根本就不使用它。
But just to be super safe,
I don't use it with primitives at all.
所以如果我真的要检查的是这个阵列
So if I was really trying to check is
this reference to the array the same as
这个对数组的引用，我不会使用双等号。
this reference to the array,
I'm not gonna use the double equals.
虽然它会在那个特定的中心工作
Even though it would work in
that one specific center,
它离边缘足够近它不值得
it's close enough to the edge
that it's not worth it.
那是我的外卖还是我的选择好吗
That's my takeaway, or
my preference, okay?
所以在非原语使用时不要使用双等号，仅将其用于
So don't use the double equals when
they're non-primitives, only use it for
在原语之间进行强制。
coercion among the primitives.
并且绝对不使用双等于 true 或 double 等于 false。
And definitely don't use double equals
to true or double equals to false.
从本质上来说，只要允许 ToBoolean 发生，
Essentially, just allow
the ToBoolean to happen,
无论如何都是最好的结果
which is the better outcome anyway.
或者如果你真的不允许的话如果真的是真的
Or if you really can't allow that,
if it really has to exactly true or
完全是错误的，有时会这样，然后使用三重等号。
exactly false, which sometimes it does,
then use triple equals.
这是一个相对较短的列表。
This is a relatively short list.
我就会让那些关心这个问题的人
And I would make the case that any
developer that cared to learn about
这些系统可以了解这一清单并有效地做到这一点，
these systems could learn this list and
effectively do so,
在他们的代码中有效的沟通他们避免了这些问题
effectively communicate in their code
that they're avoiding these problems.